Guide to the Frederick R. Koch Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Name List
  - Egan, Pierce, 1772-1849
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Egerton, Daniel, 1834 Feb 18 (Box 19, Folder 319)
        FRKF 648
  - Elgar, Edward
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Long, Charles, 1931-34 (Box 19, Folder 320)
        FRKF 1009
      - Marsh, Harvey, 1902 Mar 13 (Box 19, Folder 321)
        FRKF 383
      - Walker, Gertrude, 1887 Dec 21 (Box 19, Folder 322)
        FRKF 759.2
    - MUSIC
      - As I Laye A-Thynkynge (song)
        - Printed title page, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 323)
          FRKF 759.1
      - Concerto, violin, orchestra, op. 61, B minor
        - Arrangement for violin and piano: corrections for first edition proof, 1910 Oct 16 (Box 19, Folder 324)
          FRKF 760
      - Part Songs, op. 53
        - There is Sweet Music: score, 1908 Jan
          FRKF 570
      - Symphony, no. 3, op. 88
        - Fragment of a draft in short score, [1933] (Box 19, Folder 325)
          FRKF 763
      - Through the Long Days (song)
        - Printed title page, n.d.
  - Eugénie, Empress, consort of Napoleon III, Emperor of the French
    See also: Napoleon III, Emperor of the French/Other Papers/Album compiled by Baron Pierre de Bourgoing, box 47, folder 939
    See also: Napoleon III, Emperor of the French/Other Papers/Album compiled by Baron Pierre de Bourgoing, box 158, folder 1500
    See also: Napoleon III, Emperor of the French/Other Papers/Album compiled by Baron Pierre de Bourgoing, box 328, folder 1820
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Stendhal, [1839], [1840] (Box 19, Folder 326)
        Includes letter from Francisca Portocarrero y Palafox to Stendhal
        FRKF 1368
  - Evans, Treyer
    - DRAWINGS
      - "Wot's He Sayin' Bob?" (cartoon): in pen-and-ink
        FRKF 107
  - Falla, Manuel de
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Chaumont-Quitry, Madame de, 1920 Feb 3 (Box 19, Folder 327)
        FRKF 1077
      - Debussy, Claude, 1916 May 14 (Box 19, Folder 328)
        FRKF 541
      - [Debussy, Emma?], 1924 Apr 15 (Box 19, Folder 329)
        FRKF 724.5
      - Diaghilev, Serge, 1919 Apr-Jul (Box 19, Folder 330)
        FRKF 304
        FRKF 305
        FRKF 306
      - Evans, Edwin, 1921, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 331)
        FRKF 1013
        FRKF 1018
      - Jean-Aubry, G. (Georges), 1910-35 (Box 19, Folder 332-333)
        FRKF 542, FRKF 543, FRKF 724, FRKF 725, FRKF 764.1-7, FRKF 842, FRKF 1054, FRKF 1055, FRKF 1078, FRKF 1127, FRKF 1147
      - Roland-Manuel, 1938 Apr 17 (Box 19, Folder 334)
        FRKF 1194
      - Unidentified, 1930 Jul 7 (Box 19, Folder 335)
        Possibly to Misia Sert
        FRKF 1128
    - MUSIC
      - Soneto a Córdoba (song, voice and harp or piano)
        - Score in copyist's manuscript, with revisions in holograph, 1927
          FRKF 841
  - Fauré, Gabriel
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Beaunier, André
        See: Raunay, Jeanne, box 20, folder 339
      - Chaumont-Quitry, Madame de, [1897 Jul 2?] (Box 20, Folder 336)
        FRKF 471
      - Faure, Gabriel, 1923 Jun 27 (Box 20, Folder 336a)
        FRKF 475
      - Fuchs, Henriette, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 337)
        FRKF 475.1
      - Girard, Madame, 1899-1919, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 338)
        FRKF 980
      - Raunay, Jeanne, [1917-18] (Box 20, Folder 339)
        Includes letter to Raunay and André Beaunier
        FRKF 1116
        FRKF 1117
      - Rehberg, Willy, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 340)
        FRKF 475.2
      - Unidentified, 1910-19 (Box 20, Folder 341)
        FRKF 472
        FRKF 473
        FRKF 474
    - MUSIC
      - Andante, violin, piano, op. 75, B-flat major
        See: Violin and piano music, box 252, folder 1594
      - Berceuse, violin, piano, op. 16, D major
      - Dolly (suite, piano, 4 hands)
        - Berceuse, early version: parts for two pianos, notated on facing pages, [ca. 1862]
          FRKF 679.1
      - Mai (song)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 679.2
      - Mazurka, piano, op. 32, B-flat major
        - Music for piano, n.d.
          FRKF 679.5
      - Nocturne, piano, no. 5, op. 37, B-flat major
      - Puisque j'ai mis ma lèvre (song)
        - Score, 1863 Oct 26
          Includes unidentified sketch
          FRKF 679.4
      - Rêve d'amour (song)
        - Score, 1864 May 5
          FRKF 679.3
      - Sonata, piano
        - Music for piano, 1863 Apr 6
          FRKF 1107
      - Valse de Faust (violin, flute, and piano)
        Transcription of Gounod, Charles, Faust. Valse
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 678
      - Violin and piano music
        - Music, various works, bound in a volume, 1884, n.d.
          Andante, violin, piano, op. 75, B-flat major, violin part, n.d.
          Berceuse, violin, piano, op. 16, D major, draft, and violin part, n.d.
          Nocturne, piano, no. 5, op. 37, B-flat major, music for piano, 1884 Aug
          Unidentified, sketches, n.d.
          FRKF 901a-c
      - Unidentified
        See: Puisque j'ai mis ma lèvre (song), box 321, folder 1728
  - Feydeau, Georges
    - WRITINGS
      - Monologues
        "Le potache"
        "La petite révoltée"
        "Ma cuisinière"
        "Le mouchoir"
        "Le mouchoir!"
        FRKF 959
  - Flaubert, Gustave
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Colet, Louise, 1853 May-Dec (Box 20, Folder 342)
        FRKF 459
        FRKF 460
      - Feydeau, Ernest, [1858-ca. 59] (Box 20, Folder 343)
        FRKF 935
        FRKF 936
  - Fougasse
    - DRAWINGS
      - "Official Extravagance" (cartoon): in pen-and-ink
        FRKF 108
      - "A Sense of Direction" (cartoon): in pen-and-ink
        FRKF 98
  - Fouquier-Tinville, Antoine Quentin
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Pommier, Rabau, [1793 Oct 9]
        Dated "18 du premier mois...an 2eme"
        Accompanied by six prints of portraits of Fouquier-Tinville
        FRKF 988
  - Franck, César
    - MUSIC
      - Aimer (song)
        - Score, 1849 Feb 28
          FRKF 1031
      - Les béatitudes (oratorio)
        - Score, including piano accompaniment, 1879 Jul 10
          FRKF 646
      - Rébecca (oratorio)
        - Excerpts in short score, 1881 Mar 17
          FRKF 1032
  - Frederick II, King of Prussia
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Braunschweig, Karl, Herzog von, 1732 Apr 23 (Box 20, Folder 344)
        Accompanied by a facsimile
        FRKF 1282
      - Charles VII, King of Naples
        See: Charles VII, King of the Two Sicilies, box 20, folders 345-346
      - Charles VII, King of the Two Sicilies (Charles III, King of Spain), 1739-1758 (Box 20, Folder 345-346)
        Includes letter to the Marquis de Montallegre
        FRKF 1288
      - Ferdinand, Prince of Prussia, 1772 Mar 25 (Box 20, Folder 347)
        FRKF 835
      - Ferdinand I, King of the Two Sicilies, 1762-86 (Box 20, Folder 348-351)
      - Ferdinand IV, King of Naples
        See: Ferdinand I, King of the Two Sicilies, box 20, folders 348-351
      - Frederick William I, King of Prussia, 1736 Nov 2 (Box 20, Folder 352)
        FRKF 1283
      - Fredersdorf, Michael Gabriel, [1747 Mar] 4 (Box 20, Folder 353)
        FRKF 1285
      - Other correspondents, 1757-84 (Box 20, Folder 354)
        FRKF 833
        FRKF 837
        FRKF 838
        FRKF 1287
      - Unidentified, 1740, 1779 (Box 20, Folder 355)
        FRKF 836
        FRKF 1284
    - WRITINGS
      - Les matinées royales: copyist's manuscript, n.d.
        FRKF 851
  - French, Annie
    - DRAWINGS
      - "While Listening to the 'Wireless'" (album): drawings in pen-and-ink and watercolor, 1940
        FRKF 1421
  - Friedrich Wilhelm, Elector of Brandenburg
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Fragment of a document, 1659 Mar 30 (Box 20, Folder 356)
  - Gabillon, Ludwig
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 357)
        FRKF 824b
  - Galsworthy, John
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Hecht, W., 1928 Nov 2 (Box 20, Folder 358)
        FRKF 435b
  - Garden, Mary
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Brasseur, Jules, [1908 Apr 23] (Box 20, Folder 359)
        FRKF 535b
  - Genet, Jean
    - WRITINGS
      - Les bonnes (play): typescript carbon, corrected, n.d.
        FRKF 1248d
      - Enfant criminelle, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 360)
        FRKF 1369
      - Letter to "le préfet de police," concerning Le balcon, with related notes by Jean-Paul Sartre, [1957] (Box 20, Folder 361)
        FRKF 1248b
      - Notes on homosexuality, in the form of a letter to Jean-Paul Sartre, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 362)
        FRKF 1248a
  - Gérard, Rosamonde
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Saudemont, André
        See: Writings/Causerie on the theater, box 20, folder 363
    - WRITINGS
      - Causerie on the theater, [1945] (Box 20, Folder 363)
        Accompanied by a letter from Gérard to André Saudemont, [1945 Nov 27]
        FRKF 716c
  - German, Edward, Sir
    - MUSIC
      - Just So Song Book (songs)
        - Rolling Down to Rio: score, [1903]
          Signed by Rudyard Kipling
          FRKF 366
  - Gesvres, Léon Potier, duc de
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Legal document, 1703 Jul 9
  - Gide, André
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Cocteau, Jean, 1945 Mar 11 (Box 20, Folder 364)
        FRKF 424
      - Proust, Marcel, [1921]-22 (Box 20, Folder 365)
        FRKF 1381
        FRKF 1382
        FRKF 1383
    - WRITINGS
      - "Oscar Wilde", [1901]
        FRKF 90
  - Gilbert, W. S. (William Schwenck)
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Brough, Lionel, 1888 Jul 17 (Box 20, Folder 366)
        FRKF 19
      - Hecht, W., 1904 May 11 (Box 20, Folder 367)
        FRKF 435a
      - Poyser, Arthur, 1908 Apr 6
        Mounted on album leaf with: Sullivan, Arthur, Sir, list of characters from Ivanhoe
        FRKF 779a-b
  - Giono, Jean
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Auric, Georges, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 368)
        Appended to "Poeme extrait de ... accompagnés de la flûte de Jean Giono," typescript
        FRKF 1047e
  - Giordano, Umberto
    - MUSIC
      - Marina (opera)
        - Score, [ca. 1889]
          FRKF 1182
  - Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich
    - MUSIC
      - Finskaia fantaziia (orchestra)
        - Score, 1910 Feb 20
          FRKF 225
      - Unidentified
        - "Einlage zur variation 3/4 im Todtentanz von F. Lizst [i.e Franz Liszt]": fragment of music for piano, 1931 Apr 24
          FRKF 1149
  - Gounod, Charles
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Daudet, Alphonse, 1880 Jun 21 (Box 20, Folder 369)
        FRKF 1161
      - Hainl, Georges, 1860 Sep 14 (Box 20, Folder 370)
        FRKF 1408
      - Halévy, Léonie, 1872 Jun 7 (Box 20, Folder 371)
        FRKF 693
      - Halévy, Ludovic, 1882-83, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 372)
        FRKF 694
      - Unidentified, 1874, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 373)
        Includes: Letter possibly to Georges Bizet Letter annotated by Ludovic Halévy
        FRKF 694.5
        FRKF 812
    - MUSIC
      - Cantique pour la fête de tous les saints
        Composed in 1841 for Charles Gay Previously described in Giroud Catalogue as "La Toussaint. Hymne sacré"
        - Score, [1857]
          FRKF 384
      - Choeur de chasseurs (Où sommes-nous?) (partsong)
        - Part for first bass, [1855?]
          FRKF 993
      - La communion des Saints (soprano and orchestra)
        Text after Frédéric Mistral; composed 1889; first performed 1891 Previously described in Giroud Catalogue as "Unidentified work for piano four-hands"
        - Version for piano, 4 hands: score
          FRKF 575b
      - George Dandin (opera)
        - Fragments, [1873-74]
          FRKF 1304
      - Lutter, aimer (chorus, TTBB)
        - Score, [ca. 1880?]
          FRKF 575a
      - Le médecin malgré lui (opera)
        - Score, 1857
          FRKF 1401
      - "O Sanctissima"
        See: Sicilian mariner's hymn (mezzo soprano, tenor, organ), box 322, folder 1742
      - La reine de Saba (opera)
        - List of sections, [late 1850s] (Box 20, Folder 374)
          Annotation by Ludovic Halévy
          FRKF 692a
      - Sicilian mariner's hymn (mezzo soprano, tenor, organ)
        Previously described in Giroud Catalogue as "O Sanctissima"
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 811
      - "La Toussaint"
        See: Cantique pour la fête de tous les saints, box 322, folder 1738
      - Unidentified
        See: La communion des Saints (soprano and orchestra), box 322, folder 1740
    - WRITINGS
      - Eulogy for Georges Bizet, [1875 Jun] (Box 20, Folder 375)
        Accompanied by note from Anna Gounod to Ludovic Halévy
        FRKF 692c
    - DRAWINGS
      - Profile of a woman: in pencil, 1880 Apr 30 (Box 20, Folder 376)
        Note by Ludovic Halévy appended
        FRKF 692b
  - Granados, Enrique
    - MUSIC
      - Cartas de amor (piano)
        - Fragment of music for piano, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 377)
          Accompanied by letter from Antoni Carreras to Jack Bornoff, 1982 Mar 22
          FRKF 442
  - Greenaway, Kate
    - DRAWINGS
      - [Flower girls]: in pencil with watercolor, 1896 (Box 20, Folder 378)
        Dated "Christmas, 1896"
        FRKF 962
  - Grieg, Edvard
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Schjelderup, Gerhard Rosenkrone, 1906 Jul-Dec (Box 20, Folder 379)
        FRKF 327
        FRKF 328
  - Guilbert, Yvette
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Bertrand, Eugène, [1897], n.d. (Box 20, Folder 380)
        FRKF 695
      - Halévy, Ludovic, [1897 Oct 20] (Box 20, Folder 381)
        FRKF 695.5
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Clippings, [1892 Apr 11-15] (Box 20, Folder 382)
        Annotations by Ludovic Halévy
  - Guitry, Sacha
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - [Achard, Marcel?]
        See: Writings/ Je t'aime!, box 106, folder 1448
      - Hahn, Reynaldo, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 383)
        On verso: autograph letter, signed, from Hahn to an unidentified recipient
        FRKF 658.5
    - WRITINGS
      - Je t'aime! (play), with drawings, [1919]
        Accompanied by letter to [Marcel Achard?], n.d.
        FRKF 1367
      - Un monde fou (play): drafts
        FRKF 948
  - Hahn, Reynaldo
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Albaret, Céleste, [1922 Nov] (Box 21, Folder 384)
        FRKF 1384
      - Astruc, Gabriel, [1913 Jul 13] (Box 21, Folder 385)
        FRKF 1150
      - Bondeville, Emmanuel, [1923?] (Box 21, Folder 386)
        FRKF 1130
      - Carré, Albert, [1900-ca. 12] (Box 21, Folder 387)
        FRKF 1163
        FRKF 1164
        FRKF 1166
      - Detaille, Edouard, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 388)
        FRKF 476
      - Donnay, Maurice, [1934-35] (Box 21, Folder 389)
        FRKF 854
        FRKF 1118
        FRKF 1329
      - Herleroy, Marguerite, [1920]-45, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 390)
        FRKF 669
      - Hervieu, Paul, [1911], n.d. (Box 21, Folder 391)
        FRKF 1119
      - Klingsor, Tristan, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 392)
        FRKF 1130.1
      - Lapauze, Henry, Madame, [1911-14], n.d. (Box 21, Folder 393)
        FRKF 731
      - Lemaire, Madeleine-Jeanne Coll, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 394)
        FRKF 814
      - Loti, Pierre, [1899 Feb?] (Box 21, Folder 395)
        FRKF 1162
      - Moret, Ernest, [1892-98], n.d. (Box 21, Folder 396-399)
        FRKF 643
      - Proust, Marcel, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 400)
        FRKF 1181
      - Weil, Ann, 1910 [Mar 23] (Box 21, Folder 401)
        FRKF 1168.1
      - Other correspondents, [ca. 1914]-[27], n.d. (Box 21, Folder 402)
        FRKF 1150.5
        FRKF 1167
      - Unidentified, [1908-40?], n.d. (Box 21, Folder 403)
        FRKF 732
        FRKF 813
        FRKF 854.5
        FRKF 947.1a-b
        FRKF 947.2
        FRKF 1130.2
        FRKF 1165
        FRKF 1168
        FRKF 1168.2
    - MUSIC
      - Les feuilles blessés (songs)
        - Scores, holograph and printed, 1901-06
          Holograph scores:
          Encor sur le pavé sonne mon pas nocturne
          Dans le ciel est dressé le chêne séculaire
          Quand reviendra l'automne avec ses feuilles mortes (2 manuscripts)
          Belle lune d'argent
          Quand je viendrai m'asseoir
          Eau printannière
          Donc vous allez fleurir encor
          Compagne de l'éther
          Printed scores (Paris: Au Ménestrel):
          Pendant que je médite
          Roses en bracelet
          Aux rayons du couchant
          Bound with: L'obscurité (chorus), score, 1897, and printed score (Paris: Au Ménestrel, n.d.)
          FRKF 1422a-d
      - Ivresse (piano)
        - Music for piano, 1906-09
          FRKF 1126
      - L'obscurité (chorus)
        See: Les feuilles blessés, box 108, folder 1450
      - Songs and piano music
        - Scores, music for piano, and notes, bound in a volume, [1888?]-91, n.d.
          Holograph music:
          Adoration (song)
          Aubade espagnole (songs)
          Comme un cri (song)
          Contour mélodique improvisé (piano)
          Fleur de mon âme (song)
          Good-bye (piano)
          Improvisazione (piano)
          L'incrédule (song)
          Mai (songs)
          Notturno alla Italiana (piano)
          Offrande (song)
          Pièces d'amour (piano)
          Portrait (piano)
          Regrets (piano)
          Rêverie (song) Si mes vers avaient des ailes (song)
          Tristesse (piano)
          Printed music (Paris: G. Hartmann):
          Aubade espagnole
          Mai
          Rêverie
          Si mes vers avaient des ailes
          Most from the collection of Cléo Mérode
          FRKF 1111a-q
    - WRITINGS
      - Diary, 1897-99
        FRKF 853
      - Diary concerning Sarah Bernhardt, 1901-02
        FRKF 852
  - Halévy, F.
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      Some correspondence annotated by Ludovic Halévy
      - Halévy, Alexandrine, [1842?]-50, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 404)
        Parts of letters written by: Halévy, Flore Halévy, Léonie Halévy, Mélanie
        Includes "A Mr. de St. Georges" (poem)
        FRKF 681.6-7
        FRKF 681.13
        FRKF 681.15
      - Halévy, Léon, [1847-58], n.d. (Box 21, Folder 405)
        Includes fragment of letter from Léonie Halévy
        FRKF 681.5
      - Halévy, Léonie, [1860 Aug] 13 (Box 21, Folder 406)
        FRKF 681.4
      - Halévy, Ludovic, [1853]-61, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 407)
        FRKF 681.8
      - Heim, François-Joseph; Heim, Madame, 1844-50, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 408)
        FRKF 681.9
        FRKF 681.17
      - Maquet, Auguste, [1851 or 1856] (Box 21, Folder 409)
        FRKF 681.11
      - Prévost-Paradol, Lucien Anatole, 1849 Aug 16 (Box 21, Folder 410)
        FRKF 681.12
      - Saint-Georges, Henri, [1840s-55], n.d. (Box 21, Folder 411)
      - Other correspondents, 1859, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 412)
        FRKF 681.10
        FRKF 681.14
        FRKF 810.5
      - Unidentified (Box 21, Folder 413)
        FRKF 681.2-3
        FRKF 689.5
    - MUSIC
      - La tentation (opera ballet)
        - Score, 1832
          Tipped in: letter from Edward N. Waters to Raymond Arthur Davies, 1957 May 13
          FRKF 579
    - WRITINGS
      - Clipping, Revue politique et littéraire, 1885 Aug 10 (Box 21, Folder 414)
      - "Notice sur la vie et les travaux de Mr. Paul Delaroche", n.d. (Box 21, Folder 415)
        FRKF 681.1
  - Halévy, Fromental
    See: Halévy, F., Box 21, folders 404-415
  - Halévy, Léon
    - WRITINGS
      - Poems, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 416)
        "L'Ecrin"
        "Les larmes du cerf"
        FRKF 681.16
  - Handel, George Frideric
    - MUSIC
      - Haec est regina virginum (antiphon)
        - Parts in hand of Giuseppe Antonio Angelini and other copyists, with annotation possibly by Handel, [1707]
          9 parts:
          Concertino (folder 1598)
          Violin I, 2 copies (folder 1598a)
          Violin II, 2 copies (folder 1598b)
          Viola (folder 1598c)
          Bass (folder 1598d)
          Soprano solo (folder 1598e)
          Organ (folder 1598f)
          Accompanied by a folder, with annotations relating to Haec est regina virginum and Te decus virgineum (folder 1598g)
          FRKF 1085a
      - Laudate pueri Dominum, HWV 237 (psalm)
        - Parts in the hand of Giuseppe Antonio Angelini and other copyists, with annotation, possibly by Handel, [1707]
          18 parts:
          Concertino (folder 1599)
          Oboe I (folder 1599a)
          Oboe II (folder 1599b)
          Violin I (folder 1599c)
          Violin II (folder 1599d)
          Viola (folder 1599e)
          Violoncello or viola da gamba (folder 1599f)
          Soprano solo I (folder 1599g)
          Soprano solo II (folder 1599h)
          Alto, chorus I (folder 1599i)
          Tenor, chorus I (folder 1599j)
          Bass, chorus I (folder 1599k)
          Soprano, chorus II (folder 1599l)
          Alto, chorus II (folder 1599m)
          Tenor, chorus II (folder 1599n)
          Bass, chorus II (folder 1599o)
          Organ, continuo (folder 1599p)
          Bass, continuo (folder 1599q)
          FRKF 1085b
      - Saeviat tellus inter rigores (motet)
        - Parts in the hand of Giuseppe Antonio Angelini and other copyists, with annotations by Handel, [1707]
          2 parts:
          Concertino (folder 1600)
          Soprano solo (folder 1600a)
          FRKF 1085c
      - Te decus virgineum, HWV 243 (antiphon)
        See also: Haec est regina virginum, box 256, folder 1598g
        - Parts in the hand of Giuseppe Antonio Angelini, [1707]
          Concertino (folder 1601)
          Violin I, 2 copies (folder 1601a)
          Violin II, 2 copies (folder 1601b)
          Violone (folder 1601c)
          Bass (folder 1601d)
          Alto solo (folder 1601e)
          Organ (folder 1601f)
          FRKF 1085d
  - Hardy, Dudley
    - DRAWINGS
      - "What Do You Say to This Glorious Landscape, Mr. B?..." (cartoon): in pen-and-ink, 1911
        FRKF 101
  - Haydn, Joseph
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - "Specifiacazione di tutte le opere," holograph, [1783 or later]
        FRKF 240
  - Hofmannsthal, Hugo von
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Unidentified, 1925 Sep 10 (Box 21, Folder 417)
        FRKF 800
    - WRITINGS
      - Elektra (play), n.d.
        FRKF 341
      - "Das Märchen der 672ten Nacht": outline and draft, 1895 Apr
        FRKF 226
  - Housman, A. E. (Alfred Edward)
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      All materials, unless otherwise indicated: FRKF 314
      - Richards, Grant (from P. H. (Philip Henry) Lee-Warner), 1914 Jul 2 (Box 21, Folder 418)
        Annotated by Housman
      - Sims, G. F. (to Perry Molstad), 1955-61, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 419)
      - Wilson, Charles, 1927 Mar-Aug (Box 21, Folder 420)
        FRKF 1268
      - Other correspondents, 1917-33 (Box 21, Folder 421)
      - Unidentified, 1920, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 422)
  - Hüe, Georges Adolphe
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 423)
        FRKF 1163.5
  - Hugo, Jean
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Lemarchand, Jacques, 1924 Jun 23 (Box 21, Folder 424)
        FRKF 1245.A09
  - Hugo, Valentine
    - OTHER PAPERS
      All materials: FRKF 534
      - Album amicorum, 1919-20, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 425-426)
        Includes inscriptions, poems, and music quotations by: Auric, Georges, Marie Laurencin and unidentified music Cocteau, Jean "Théâtre" and drawings Mater, André Poulenc, Francis, La carpe Radiguiet, Raymond, "Initiales" Satie, Erik Thomas, Albert
      - Letters to René Berthelot concerning the Album amicorum, 1970-83 (Box 22, Folder 427)
        Includes letters from: Auric, Georges Hugo, Jean Marais, Jean Milhaud, Darius
      - Printed invitation to the funeral of Georges Auric, 1983 Nov 22 (Box 22, Folder 428)
  - Hugo, Victor
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      See also: Other Papers/Album relating to Victor Hugo, box 113, folder 1455
      See also: Other Papers/Album relating to Victor Hugo, box 352, folder 2080
      - Unidentified, 1869 May 7 (Box 22, Folder 429)
        FRKF 937
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Album relating to Victor Hugo, 1821-[70s], n.d.
        Correspondence of Hugo includes:
        Béranger, Pierre Jean de (to Hugo)
        Boulanger, Louis-Alexis
        Custine, Astolphe, marquis de
        Hugo, Charles Victor
        Joanny, Jean-Baptiste (to Hugo)